Keita Nonaka

WEB DEVELOPER

Details

Kobe, 652-0047 Japan +81 90 5883 5402

moonrider.crowdworks@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

1994-08-19

Links

linkedin

Skills

Communication Skills

Software Logic

Database Management

PHP(Laravel)

ES6(MERN, MEVN)

Python(Django)

ML, AI

Languages

English

Chinese

Profile

Experienced Web Developer adept in all stages of advanced web development. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set, including modern JS, PHP frameworks and AI.

Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Employment History

Junior Fullstack Developer, YEXI NETWORK TECH CO., LTD., Shanghai

APRIL 2015 - MARCH 2017

- Created a reusable component library for the web application using Vuejs, resulting in faster development time for new features
- Developed a real-time notification system that kept users informed of the latest updates and events

Senior Fullstack Developer, DATAPYRAMID, Shenzhen

APRIL 2017 - APRIL 2020

- Developed a system to monitor application performance and alert stakeholders of any potential issues
- Created an API gateway that improved system performance by 10% and reduced latency by 5%
- Generated reports and provided analytics on accounts payable to senior management, resulting in improved budget forecasting

Fullstack developer, Lancers.jp, Kobe

MAY 2020

- Developed a custom UI library that increased developer productivity and code reuse
- Implemented a microservices architecture that improved system modularity and reduced dependencies between components
- · Refactored legacy code to improve reliability, scalability and maintainability

Education

Master, Shanghai Jiaotong University, Shanghai

APRIL 2011 - MARCH 2015

Awarded the Master's degree in Computer Science.